Write a program that can be used to calculate the federal tax. The tax is calculated as follows: For single people, the standard exemption is $4,000; for married people, the standard exemption is $7,000. A person can also put up to 6% of his or her gross income in a pension plan. The tax rates are as follows: If the taxable income is:

Between $0 and $15,000, the tax rate is 15%.
Between $15,001 and $40,000, the tax is $2,250 plus 25% of the taxable income over $15,000.
Over $40,000, the tax is $8,460 plus 35% of the taxable income over $40,000. Prompt the user to enter the following information:
Marital status
If the marital status is “married,” ask for the number of children under the age of 14
Gross salary (If the marital status is “married” and both spouses have income, enter the combined salary.)
Percentage of gross income contributed to a pension fund Your program must consist of at least the following functions:
Function getData: This function asks the user to enter the relevant data.
Function taxAmount: This function computes and returns the tax owed.
To calculate the taxable income, subtract the sum of the standard exemption, the amount contributed to a pension plan, and the personal exemption, which is $1,500 per person. (Note that if a married couple has two children under the age of 14, then the personal exemption is $1,500 ∗ 4 = $6,000.)

Grading
When you have completed your program, click the Submit button to record your score.





Tasks
10.00
out of
10.00
Program Outputs Correctly

0
4 out of 4 checks passed. Great work!

Checks
Code PatternComplete
Contains getData function

Description
Searched your code for a specific pattern:

void.+getData\(

You can learn more about regular expressions here.

Code PatternComplete
Contains taxAmount function

Description
Searched your code for a specific pattern:

double.+taxAmount\(

You can learn more about regular expressions here.

Test CaseComplete
Successful Output

Input
m
5
50000
6
Output
Enter marital status: m or M (married), s or S (single): m

Enter number of children under the age of 14: 5

Enter gross salary for the year: 50000

Enter percentage of salary contributed to pension (0-6 percent): 6


Your tax for the year is: 5875.00

Results
5875.00
Expected Output
5875.00
Test CaseComplete
Successful Output II

Input
s
250001
6
Output
Enter marital status: m or M (married), s or S (single): s

Enter gross salary for the year: 250001

Enter percentage of salary contributed to pension (0-6 percent): 6


Your tax for the year is: 74785.33

Results
74785.33
Expected Output
74785.33