Instructions:

Write a program using a while loop that lets the user enter a series of integers, followed by -99 to //signal the end of the series. After all the numbers have been entered, the program should display the //largest and smallest numbers entered.

Some tips to consider:

1. you can initialize your sentinel variable to -99. 

2. initialize the largest and smallest variables to the first number (before the loop).

example:

     greatest = least = num;

3. use if else inside your loop to determine the greatest and least number.

4. make sure to get the next number inside the loop.

SAMPLE RUN:


Enter an integer (or -99 to quit): 5

Enter another integer (or -99 to quit): 10


The  largest number you entered was --

The smallest number you entered was --

You may collaborate with a partner.
